# **Dani Drury**

## **SUMMARY**

Versatile and analytical problem-solver with strong communication, quantitative, and technical skills. As I pursue a career change into the tech industry, I offer employers a diverse range of strengths and experience combined with a strong work ethic, integrity, and passionate enthusiasm for learning.

## **EDUCATION**

- UC Berkeley Coding Bootcamp, Oct 2023-April 2024 Full Stack Web Development Certificate
- De Anza College, 2023 Coursework Completed: Calculus III (Math 1C, Math 1D)
- **Purdue University**, 1998-2003 Bachelor of Liberal Arts in English

## **SKILLS**

**Technical:** JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Node.js, Express.js, React, HTMX, MySQL, Sequelize.js, MongoDB, Mongoose.js, VS Code, Git, GitHub, Slack, Microsoft OS, MS Office, Google Workspace **Soft:** Communication (written and verbal), Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Relationship Building, Self-Learning, Leadership, Organization

## **PROJECTS**

• **PropertyPlus Care** – Deployed Application: <a href="https://property-plus-care-557bf1c35b3f.herokuapp.com/">https://property-plus-care-557bf1c35b3f.herokuapp.com/</a> **Github Repo:** <a href="https://github.com/stephen-scheiman/PropertyPlus-Care">https://github.com/stephen-scheiman/PropertyPlus-Care</a>

**Description:** Full-stack bootcamp group project - property maintenance management web app. RESTful API with CRUD functionality intended to streamline maintenance management with improved accountability via a daily, task-based, follow-up system.

Roles: Concept creator, back-end coder, CSS contributor

Technologies Used: Node.js, Expess.js, HTMX, Handlebars.js, Tailwind CSS, HTML5, Sequelize.js

• Entertainment Search Website – Deployed Application: <a href="https://danidrury.github.io/entertainment-search/">https://danidrury.github.io/entertainment-search/</a> Github Repo: <a href="https://github.com/DaniDrury/entertainment-search">https://github.com/DaniDrury/entertainment-search</a>

**Description:** Front-end bootcamp group project highlighting API usage. Responsive, user-friendly interface for searching TV Shows, Movies and Entertainers.

Role: Project Manager, Lead Design & CSS coder, contributing JavaScript coder

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Pure CSS framework, Bootstrap modal component

## **EXPERIENCE**

Dillon Beach Property Management, Inc., 2018 - Present

Role: Tech Solutions Architect

#### **Responsibilities & Accomplishments:**

- Assist in operating and growing a small vacation rental property management business by serving in key roles such as software integration specialist, revenue manager, IT support, and inventory acquisition.
- Utilize in-depth understanding of the company and industry to identify, design, and implement processes and technologies that streamline operations, grow inventory, and increase revenue.
- Directly contributed to a 111% increase in gross rental revenue over two years through effective market data analysis and revenue management strategies.

**Graton Resort & Casino** | Dual Rate Floor Supervisor | Rohnert Park, CA — 2013-2018 **French Lick Resort & Casino** | Table Games Dealer | French Lick, IN — 2006-2012 **Liberty Mutual Insurance** | Claims Case Manager II | Carmel, IN — 2003-2006

<sup>\*</sup> Additional work experience details available upon request